hbonordic.com 2016-04-14

# HBO Nordic

## Processing of Personal Data

### Together with the User Terms and Conditions, this Personal Data Policy comprises the terms and conditions governing the User's agreement with HBO.

#### 1 Generally

HBO Nordic AB (hereinafter "HBO"), company registration no. 556865-2845, Kungsträdgårdsgatan 20, 11147, Stockholm, is the data controller of personal data processed within the framework of this policy. HBO processes the User's personal data in accordance with the Swedish Personal Data Act (Swedish Code of Statutes 1998:204). By registering a user account, the User consents to HBO processing such User's personal data in accordance with the provisions below.

#### 2 What personal data is processed?

The personal data which is processed is the information provided by the User in conjunction with registration of Accounts with HBO, in conjunction with expressions of interest or other contacts with HBO, and information provided by the User for survey purposes. This personal data also includes names, addresses, telephone numbers, e-mail addresses, debit card and credit card information and personal identification numbers. Following execution of the Agreement, HBO may collect information regarding the User's creditworthiness and otherwise supplement the personal data to the extent allowed by applicable laws by obtaining information from public and private registers for the purpose of updating its user register with personal data which is deemed necessary in order to properly service customers and maintain its registers.

#### 3 Purpose

HBO processes personal data in order for HBO and HBO's licensor to be able to perform the Agreement with the User, to analyse operations and customer behaviour, for customer administration, as a basis for charging for the Service, in order to provide offers, information and news to the User, to communicate with the User and in order for HBO to be able to fulfil its obligations according to law. HBO will also use personal data for direct marketing or other advertising via e-mail and other channels of HBO and, subject to the User's explicit consent, other companies' services and products.

Personal data may, subject to the User's explicit consent, be provided to other companies within the HBO group and to companies with which the group cooperates for direct advertising or other advertising via e-mail or another channel of services and products of HBO, companies within the HBO group or other companies and for market surveys.

HBO may also provide your personal data to companies which perform services for HBO in order for such companies to be able to perform the services requested by HBO. Such companies may be located in countries outside the European Union and European Economic Area where the level of data protection may not be as comprehensive as in your jurisdiction. The services which may be requested are, for example, the provision of infrastructure and IT services, the provision of customer services, the processing of market surveys and the performance of statistical analyses and processing of credit card and debit card transactions.

#### 4 Blocked marketing

In the event the User desires that the User's personal data not be processed for purposes relating to direct marketing, notice thereof may be given to:  
HBO Nordic AB  
Kungsträdgårdsgatan 20  
111 47, Stockholm.

E-mail: kundtjanst@hbonordic.com

Telephone no. 0770-455 000

The notice must contain information regarding the User's name and personal identification number.

#### 5 Access to information

The User shall be entitled, once per calendar year, to obtain without cost information regarding the personal data HBO processes regarding the User, the source of the data, the use of the data, and the identity of parties to whom the data has been provided. Such request must be in writing, signed by the User, and contain the User's name and personal identification number. Such requests shall be sent to the address set forth in section 4 above.

The User shall be entitled at any time to request a correction of any erroneous or modified information.

#### 6 Cookies

HBO uses so-called cookies on the Website in order to provide the User access to certain functions and in order to obtain information regarding visits to the Website.

_What are cookies?_  
A cookie is a small text file which is stored on the User's computer and which contains information. There are two types of cookies. One type of cookie is a so-called permanent cookie which saves a file permanently on the User's computer until the file is removed. The other type of cookie is called a session cookie which disappears when the User closes his or her web browser.

_What are cookies used for?_  
Session cookies are sent between the User's computer and HBO's server in order to keep track of information regarding the User such as, for example, which user name is used.

HBO uses permanent cookies, among other things, to make it easier for the User to use the Service by providing the User with access to stored information, in order to obtain information regarding the use of the Service by individual users, and to recommend films and TV series which are appropriate to the User's interests.

Anonymised information from permanent cookies is also used for statistical purposes such as maintaining statistics regarding the use of the Website, to conduct surveys in order to improve the Service, in order to determine which parts of the Service are most popular, in order to provide information to third parties so that appropriate advertising may be directed to the User, and to optimize the use of the Website.

HBO also uses the following third-party cookies  
Google Analytics – cookies used to collect information regarding the manner in which the User uses the Website, e.g. which parts the User visits most frequently, in order to analyze the use of the Website and to improve user experience. More information is available at: <https://developers.google.com/analytics/resources/concepts/gaConceptsCookies>

Marketo – cookies are used to recognize the User when the User returns to the Website and to gather information regarding the use of the Website in order to provide information to the User in accordance with his or her interests. More information is available at: <http://www.marketo.com/privacy.php>

Snoobi – cookies are used to gather information regarding the manner in which the User uses the Website, e.g. which parts are visited most frequently, in order to analyze the use of the Website and improve user experience. More information is available at: [http://www.snoobi.com/privacy/snoobi+privacy+policy/](http://www.snoobi.fi/kayttoehdot/tietosuoja/)

_How can the User remove cookies?_  
The User can choose whether he or she wishes to accept cookies. By adjusting the web browser, the User may avoid receiving cookies. However, this might cause failure in the function of the Service. The method used to block cookies will depend on the web browser used. Consult the "Help" or corresponding menu in the web browser for instructions.

For more detailed information regarding cookies, please go to [www.pts.se](http://www.pts.se/).
